My Steiff

Wishlist

Shopping cart

Privacy Policy
==============

Steiff USA (“Steiff,” “our,” “us,” or “we”) is committed to protecting the privacy and security of the information of our website visitors (“you”). We want you to understand how we collect and use information from our website, www.steiffusa.com (the “Site”) and our related services, (together with the Site, the “Services”) so you can interact with us with confidence. By using the Services, you accept and agree to the practices this Privacy Policy describes. If you do not agree to any of the terms in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Services.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When you use our Services, we may collect, store, and process various kinds of data, including Personal Information about you. “Personal Information” refers to information about you that can be used to identify you, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card information, or transaction information.

Specifically, we may collect, store, or process information when you:

* Register on our Site;
* Place an order, return an item, or make an exchange;
* Submit a form on the Site;
* Contact us with inquiries, including via email;
* Subscribe to our newsletter or otherwise sign up to receive communications;
* Respond to a survey;
* Enter contests or sweepstakes; or
* Voluntarily provide information.

We may also collect details of your visit to our Site and the pages you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, including your IP address, browser type, the date and time you accessed or left the Sites, and which pages you viewed. Some parts of our Site uses cookies and other technologies to collect this information about your general internet usage. See the section below called “How We Use Cookies” to learn more.

**Why We Collect Information**

We use your information for the following purposes:

* To present our Services to you;
* To process transactions;
* To personalize your experience;
* To provide you with information, products or services, including customer service that you request from us;
* To administer a contest, promotion, survey, or other Site feature;
* To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it;
* To notify you about changes to our products or Services we offer;
* To allow you to participate in any interactive features on our Services;
* In any other way we may describe when you provide the information;
* To improve our Services;
* To perform analytics to learn about the behavior of our Service users;
* To send periodic emails relating to your order, occasional company news, updates, or related product information;
* With your permission, we may send you marketing emails about our Services, new products and other updates;
* For any other purpose with your consent;
* To evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us about our Site visitors is among the assets transferred.

**How We Use Tracking Technologies**

* We use cookies (small text files stored in your browser) and other techniques such as web beacons (small, clear picture files used to follow your online activities) (“Tracking Technologies”). Tracking Technologies collect information that tells us how you use our Site, web-related products and Services. The use of Tracking Technologies does not give us access to the rest of your computer.
* This, in turn, helps us make our Services relevant to your interests and needs. We use both first-party Tracking Technologies and third-party Tracking Technologies.
* Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information
* We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:
    * Tracking Technologies and Advertising. Most browsers accept cookies automatically. You may be able to set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. For instructions, check your browser’s technical information. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this Site may then be inaccessible or not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service. Please note that cookie-based opt outs must be performed on each device and browser that you wish to have opted out.
    * Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising. If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can always opt-out by logging into the Site and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to [support@steiffusa.com](mailto:support@steiffusa.com).
    * Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your e-mail address/contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by clicking the unsubscribe link in the promotional email. This opt out does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of a product purchase, warranty registration, product service experience or other transactions.
    * Targeted or Interest-Based Advertising. We may work with third-party advertising companies that collect and use information about your online activities across sites over time, in order to deliver more relevant advertising when you are visiting the Site and elsewhere on the Internet. This practice is known as interest-based advertising. The online advertising industry also provides websites from which you may opt-out of receiving targeted ads from our advertising partners that participate in self-regulatory programs. You can access these, and also learn more about targeted advertising and consumer choice and privacy at: [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), [www.youronlinechoices.eu/](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) or [www.youradchoices.ca/](http://www.youradchoices.ca/), and [www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Note that electing to opt out will not stop advertising from appearing in your browser or applications. It may make the ads you see less relevant to your interests. If you delete, block, or otherwise restrict cookies or use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.
    * Google Analytics. We may use Google Analytics to improve our Site’s functions. You can choose not to be included in Google Analytics by visiting [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**“Do Not Track” Requests**

Our Site currently does not respond to “do not track” or similar signals.

**How Do We Share Your Personal Information?**

We may disclose your Personal Information as follows:

* With affiliates, contractors, service providers, and other third-parties we use to support our business;
* To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it;
* For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information;
* With your consent;
* With affiliates if you opt-in to receiving communications from affiliates;
* To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which Personal Information held by us about the Website users is among the assets transferred;
* To enforce any agreement, including any applicable terms of service;
* To establish or exercise our right to defend against legal claims;
* To law enforcement and other government authorities such as legislatures, courts, agencies and litigants if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of governmental authorities; (b) comply with legal process; (c) respond to requests from public or government authorities, including public or government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) protect the security or integrity of the Services’ information systems; and/or (e) exercise or protect our rights, privacy, safety or those of affiliates, clients, you or others; and
* If we reasonably believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Steiff or others.

**Payment Information**

When you make a payment on our Site, you may be taken to the website of one of our third-party service providers. The service provider will either collect or have access to your first and last name, zip code, postal address, email address, payment amount, billing information, and payment card information. Please review the Privacy Policy of our third-party service provider to learn how they protect your information.

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**

To protect your Personal Information, we take commercially reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. However, no data protection procedures are entirely infallible. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee that it will be 100% secure. Your transmission of your information to our Platform thus is done entirely at your own risk.

**Third-Party Websites and Social Media**

Our Site may contain links to other sites, including those of third parties or partners. While we seek to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices other websites use. By accessing other third-party websites or applications through our Site, you are consenting to the terms and privacy policies of those websites. It is possible that other parties may collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use our Site.

Our Site may include social media features, such as Facebook “Likes” or “Recommend” buttons, Pinterest, Twitter, Tumblr, and YouTube. These social media features may require cookies to be set to function properly. These features may also collect Personal Information such as your IP address. These features are governed by the Privacy Policy of the social media platform. Please review the Privacy Policy of the social media platforms to learn how they protect your information.

**International Visitors**

Our Site may be hosted and operated outside of the United States (“US”). By using this Site, you are consenting to the transfer of your Personal Information from the US to another country.

**California Visitors**

If you are a California resident, please review the California Privacy Notice.

**Users Only of Legal Age of Majority**

Our Services are not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Services or on or through any of its features/register on the Services or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13 without verifiable parental consent, please contact us at support@steiffusa.com.

**Review and Correction of Your Information**

You may review and edit the information we collected about you at any time by contacting us at the addresses listed at the end of this privacy policy. If your information has been shared with a third party, as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, then that third party has received its own copy of your data. If you have been contacted by one of these third parties and wish to correct or delete your information, please contact them directly.

**Privacy Policy Updates**

We update the Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it regularly. If we materially change our Privacy Policy, we will notify you by contacting you through your provided e-mail address or by posting a notice on our Site. Your continued use of our Site will be deemed your agreement that your information may be used in accordance with the new policy. If you do not agree with the changes, then you should stop using the Site and notify us that you do not want your information used in accordance with the changes.

**Contacting Us**

We welcome any questions, comments, or complaints you may have regarding this Privacy Policy. Please do not hesitate to contact us by [email](mailto:support@steiffusa.com) or by writing to us:

Steiff North America

Attn: Customer Service/Privacy

24 Albion Rd. Suite 220

Lincoln, RI 02865 USA

**Phone** (International) - 401-312-0080

**Phone** (US and Canada) - 888-W-STEIFF | 888-978-3433

**For the California Privacy Notice [click here](https://www.steiff.com/en-us/i/privacy-notice-for-california-residents).**

Company

Popular Categories

Contact & Legal

Shipping partner

Pay with:

© 2024 Steiff North America Online Shop
